#### Contact

9921833071 (Mobile) shrikantpatwari@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/

shrikantpatwari (LinkedIn) awesomeebeauty.blogspot.in (Blog) stackoverflow.com/story/shrikantpatwari (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

JavaScript
Front-end Development
AngularJS

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Marathi (Full Professional)
Hindi (Full Professional)

### Certifications

Up and Running with ECMAScript 6 ES2015: The Shape of JavaScript to Come

# Shrikant Patwari

Senior Software Engineer at YuktaMedia Pune

## Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the web development industry. Skilled in Angular js, Javascript, Backbone.js, and Front-end Development with good knowledge of the backend technology like Java, PHP, Mysql etc. Strong consulting professional with a Engineer's Degree focused in Information Technology from TPCT's College of Engineering, Osmanabad.

## Experience

YuktaMedia 4 years 7 months

Senior Software Engineer April 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Full Stack Software developer working in Angular, Spring boot, Mysql, Cassandra and It Infra AWS.

Software Developer Consultant March 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 2 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Software Developer Consultant at Yukta Media, Pune working for Front End Development in Angular, Bootstrap, HTML and Javascript

Tudip Technologies Software Engineer March 2015 - February 2016 (1 year)

Demandware Developer

## Education

TPCT's College of Engineering, Osmanabad Engineer's Degree, Information Technology (2009 - 2014) Ramkrushna Paramhansa Junior College, Osmanabad Associate's Degree, Science · (2007 - 2009)

Shri. Bhosale Highschool, Osmanabad High School, Marathi · (2002 - 2007)